Mittenthal, Richard Papers 6407
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Fairchild Republic through Frito-Lay, 1969-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 21: Fort James, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    11/25/1998
  - Item 22: Franklin Lod School District (Board of Education), 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    12/6/2000
  - Item 23: Frito-Lay, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 13)
    4/22/1998
- Gallagher Industrial Laundry through Goebel Brewing, 1968-2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Gollagher Industrial Leendry of Detroit, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    1/19/1981
  - Item 2: Galoner Denver, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    8/12/1969
  - Item 3: General American Transportation, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    10/25/1983
  - Item 4: General Cable Corporation, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    9/21/1968
  - Item 5: General Cable Corporation, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    5/18/1970
  - Item 6: GE, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    7/10/2002
  - Item 7: General Telephone of Indiana, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    7/7/1970
  - Item 8: Georgia Pacific, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    4/19/1993
  - Item 9: Georgia Pacific, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    11/5/1998
  - Item 10: Gibson Refigerator, 1987; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    7/16/1987
  - Item 11: Glass Containers, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    7/12/1972
  - Item 12: Glass Containers, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    7/9/1973
  - Item 13: Glass Containers, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    6/30/1975
  - Item 14: Goebel Brewing, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 14)
    5/20/1963
- Gold Bond Building Products through Gulf States Steel, 1969-1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Gold Bond Building Products, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    3/24/1983
  - Item 2: BF Goodrich Chemical, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    4/19/1969
  - Item 3: Gould Incorporated, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    10/29/1973
  - Item 4: Gould Incorporated, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    12/26/1961
  - Item 5: Gouphees Certified Association, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Great Lakes Steamship, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    4/2/1984
  - Item 7: Al Green Enterpises, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    10/24/1960
  - Item 8: Gudeman Company, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    3/1/1958
  - Item 9: Gulf Oil Corporation, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    8/31/1964
  - Item 10: Gulf & Western Manufacturing, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    8/22/1983
  - Item 11: Gulf States Steel, 1987; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    5/21/1987
  - Item 12: Gulf States Steel, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 15)
    9/23/1991
- Hamilton Manufacturing through Howell Industries, 1969-2005 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Hamilton Manufacturing, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    1/29/1973
  - Item 1: Harbison Walke Refracories, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    8/29/1961
  - Item 2: Harneschfeger Corporation, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    7/27/1965
  - Item 2: Hanna Furniture Corporation, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    6/20/1984
  - Item 3: Harman - Motive, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    10/6/1999
  - Item 3: Hanna Mining Corporation, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    5/9/1959
  - Item 4: Hanna Mining Corporation, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    7/7/1964
  - Item 4: City of Harper Woods (fire), 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    8/12/1998
  - Item 5: Harshaw Chemical Company, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    8/4/1961
  - Item 6: Hastings Manufacturing Corporation, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    6/3/1969
  - Item 7: Hastings Manufacturing Corporation, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    8/7/1979
  - Item 8: Herty, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    9/12/2005
  - Item 9: Hewitt Soap, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    6/9/1999
  - Item 10: Hetachi Magnets, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    8/5/1997
  - Item 11: Honeyon Air, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    8/23/2003
  - Item 12: Geo A. Hormel, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 16)
    11/23/1983
- Howmet Corporation through ITT- Grinnell, 1969-2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Howmet, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    11/26/1969
  - Item 2: Huron Portland Cement, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    7/24/1959
  - Item 3: Jola Products, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    9/24/1965
  - Item 4: Ill Bell Tele, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    4/4/1969
  - Item 5: Indi\ana Forge & Machine, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    12/8/1963
  - Item 6: Indianapolis Power & Light, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    10/7/1974
  - Item 7: Industrial Experimental Technologies, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    7/9/1969
  - Item 8: Industrial Metal Products, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    12/10/1981
  - Item 9: Industrial Mutual Association, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    2/9/1966
  - Item 10: Inland Time & Stone, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    1/8/1988
  - Item 11: Inland Steel Company: Busted Mine, 1967; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    3/25/1967
  - Item 12: Inland Steel Company: Busted Mine, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    9/1/1981
  - Item 13: Interchemical Corporation: Press Tite Division, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    2/27/1969
  - Item 14: Interchemical Corporation (paint makers), 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    3/31/1969
  - Item 15: Intelake Incorporated, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    8/1/1979
  - Item 16: International Paper Company, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    6/20/2000
  - Item 17: International Salt Company, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    6/5/1961
  - Item 18: International Salt Company, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    3/8/1963
  - Item 19: International Salt Company, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    6/6/1964
  - Item 20: Invensys Precision Dry Casting, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    1/23/2002
  - Item 21: Mitchell-Bently Corporation, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    5/1/1961
  - Item 22: Itt-Grinnell Corporation, 1980; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 17)
    4/4/1980
- J and L Specialty Steel through Kelsey-Hayes, 1971-2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: J & H Speciatly Steel, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    7/18/2003
  - Item 2: James River Corporation, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    4/28/1993
  - Item 3: Jessop Steel Company, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    2/4/1976
  - Item 4: Jessop Steel Company, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    3/9/1977
  - Item 5: Johns Manville, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    6/3/2005
  - Item 6: Johnson Controls, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    7/5/1996
  - Item 7: Joslyn Mfg and Supply, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    12/22/1971
  - Item 8: Journal - Sentinel, 1990; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    12/5/1990
  - Item 9: Joy Manufacturing, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    4/8/1965
  - Item 10: Kaiser Aluminum & Chemical, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    6/4/2002
  - Item 11: Kalsec Incorporated, 1994; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    11/11/1994
  - Item 12: Kayden Corporation, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    12/9/2002
  - Item 13: Kelsey-Hayes, 1980; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 18)
    12/29/1980
- Kennecott Copper through Kroger, 1971-1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Kennecott Copper Corporation, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    1/8/1973
  - Item 2: Kennecott Copper Corporation, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    3/15/1973
  - Item 3: Kennecott Copper Corporation, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    9/30/1974
  - Item 4: Kennecott Copper Corporation, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    12/30/1974
  - Item 5: Keystone Management Company, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    2/12/1965
  - Item 6: Koppers Industries Company, 1980; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    9/29/1980
  - Item 7: Kraft Foods, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 19)
    8/31/1971
- Laclede Steel through Lyon Incorporation, 1968-2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Laclede Steel Company, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    3/2/1970
  - Item 2: Laclede Steel Company, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    8/5/1974
  - Item 3: Ladbroke Racing Michigan, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    10/7/1997
  - Item 4: Ladbroke Racing Michigan, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    7/17/1998
  - Item 5: Lake Eie Transit, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    11/18/1993
  - Item 6: Lake Shone Incorporated, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    1/27/1984
  - Item 7: Laundry Domestic - Leaner Supply Company, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    4/16/1973
  - Item 8: Lazy Boy Chairs Company, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    5/13/1964
  - Item 9: Lear Incoporated, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    10/11/1957
  - Item 10: Lear Incoporated, 1956; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    12/28/1956
  - Item 11: Lear Incoporated, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    12/24/1957
  - Item 12: Lear Incoporated, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    6/7/1958
  - Item 13: Lear Incoporated, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    1/18/1960
  - Item 14: Lear Incoporated, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    2/22/1996
  - Item 15: Leaseway Auto Corners, 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    2/18/1995
  - Item 16: Leinard Refineries, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    8/16/1961
  - Item 17: Light Metals Corporation, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    11/8/1957
  - Item 18: Light Metals Corporation, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    9/29/1959
  - Item 19: Light Metals Corporation, 1960; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    8/9/1960
  - Item 20: Light Metals Corporation, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    8/2/1965
  - Item 21: Lindell Drop Forge, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    9/29/1968
  - Item 22: City of Lavonia - Firefighters, 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    6/14/1995
  - Item 23: City of Lavonia - Firefighters, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    5/24/2000
  - Item 24: Lone Star Steel, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    6/21/1957
  - Item 25: Lyon Incorporated, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 1, Folder 20)
    7/24/1961
- MP Pumps through Metaldyne, 1969-2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: MP Pumps, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    3/9/1964
  - Item 2: Board of Trustees Community College - Macomb County, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    6/21/1969
  - Item 3: Macomb County Roads Commission, 1994; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    9/13/1994
  - Item 4: Macomb County Roads Commission, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    8/8/1997
  - Item 5: Macomb County Roads Commission, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    1/5/2000
  - Item 6: Macomb Pulblishing, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    7/7/1971
  - Item 7: Magnavox, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    7/3/1963
  - Item 8: Mascotech Forming Technologies, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    4/24/1997
  - Item 9: The McLaughlin Corporation, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    5/15/1958
  - Item 10: Mc Louth Steel, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    10/1/1957
  - Item 11: Mc Louth Steel, 1958; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    8/25/1958
  - Item 12: Mead Corporation, 1992; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    12/4/1992
  - Item 13: Melling Forging Company, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    6/30/1982
  - Item 14: Melling Forging Company, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    9/13/1982
  - Item 15: Melling Forging Company, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    9/24/1982
  - Item 16: Mennel Milling Company, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    9/7/1964
  - Item 17: Mc Laren Health Care, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    3/13/2003
  - Item 18: Mc Laren Health Care, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Metalloy Corpoation, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    9/1/2000
  - Item 20: Board of Trustees of Mercy Hospital Nurses, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    5/7/1973
  - Item 21: Menenne Beverage, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    10/10/1988
  - Item 22: Metaldyne Corporation (Auto), 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 1)
    10/12/2001
- Metalloy Corporation through Michigan Seat, 1968-2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Metalloy Corpoation (Auto), 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    10/27/1997
  - Item 2: Metals Technology Corporation, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    4/4/2002
  - Item 3: Metropolitan Hopsital, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    1/12/1979
  - Item 4: Michigan Bell Telephone, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    8/11/1975
  - Item 5: Michigan Consolidated, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    6/1/1968
  - Item 6: Michigan Consolidated, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    10/5/1968
  - Item 7: Michigan Consolidated, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    1/6/1969
  - Item 8: Michigan Consolidated, 1990; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    6/8/1990
  - Item 9: Michigan Milk Producers Association, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    8/22/1962
  - Item 10: Michigan Milk Producers Association, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    8/21/2001
  - Item 11: Michigan Panalyte Molded Plastics, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    9/1/1962
  - Item 12: Michigan Road Builders Association, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    8/15/2001
  - Item 13: Michigan Seamless Tube, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    8/5/1966
  - Item 14: Michigan Seamless Tube, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Michigan Seat Company, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 2)
    6/10/2002
- Michigan Department of Corrections through Michigan Department of Mental Health, 1981-2005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: State of Michigan Department of Corrections, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    5/28/1993
  - Item 2: State of Michigan Department of Corrections, 1994; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    11/8/1994
  - Item 3: State of Michigan Department of Corrections, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    11/11/1996
  - Item 4: State of Michigan Department of Corrections, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    11/15/1996
  - Item 5: State of Michigan Department of Corrections, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: State of Michigan Department of Corrections, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: State of Michigan Department of Corrections, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    1/18/2000
  - Item 8: State of Michigan Department of Corrections, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    1/27/2000
  - Item 9: State of Michigan Department of Corrections, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    11/9/2000
  - Item 10: State of Michigan Department of Corrections, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    6/15/2005
  - Item 11: State of Michigan Mental Health, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    9/10/1981
  - Item 12: State of Michigan Mental Health, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    12/9/1981
  - Item 13: State of Michigan Mental Health, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    11/2/1982
  - Item 14: State of Michigan Mental Health, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    2/8/1983
  - Item 15: State of Michigan Plymouth for Human Development, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    5/2/1983
  - Item 16: State of Michigan Department of Mental Health, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    6/27/1983
  - Item 17: State of Michigan Department of Mental Health, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    3/2/1984
  - Item 18: State of Michigan Department of Mental Health, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    10/18/1984
  - Item 19: State of Michigan Department of Mental Health, 1985; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    4/12/1985
  - Item 20: State of Michigan Department of Mental Health, 1985; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    9/10/1985
  - Item 21: State of Michigan Department of Mental Health, 1986; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 3)
    11/11/1986
- Michigan Department of Military Affairs through Minute Maid, 1971-2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Department of Military Affairs Air National Guard, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    9/28/2002
  - Item 2: State of Michigan Department of Social Services, 1986; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    4/28/1986
  - Item 3: Michigan Deparment of State Police, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    9/29/1998
  - Item 4: Michigan Deparment of State Police, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    11/18/1981
  - Item 5: Michigan Deparment of State Police, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    4/20/1982
  - Item 6: Michigan Deparment of State Police, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    6/11/1982
  - Item 7: Michigan Deparment of State Police, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    6/17/1983
  - Item 8: Michigan Deparment of State Police, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Michigan Deparment of State Police, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    7/5/1984
  - Item 10: State of Michgan Department of Transportation, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    5/30/1999
  - Item 11: Michigan State University, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    10/9/1969
  - Item 12: Michigan State University, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    2/16/1971
  - Item 13: Michigan State University, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    1/3/1972
  - Item 14: Michigan State University, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    1/12/1976
  - Item 15: Regents of University of Michigan (police), 1994; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    8/8/1994
  - Item 16: University of Michigan - Graduate Employees, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    1/28/1996
  - Item 17: Micrometer - Home Corporation, 1964; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    9/1/1964
  - Item 18: Mid Michigan Communit College, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    4/16/1998
  - Item 19: Miller Brewery, 1986; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    5/30/1986
  - Item 20: Minute Maide, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 4)
    11/14/2001
- Mississippi Valley Structural Steel through Muskegon Piston Ring, 1960-2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Miss Valley Structural Steel, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    5/16/1961
  - Item 2: Mobil Oil, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    2/21/1969
  - Item 3: Mobile Pulley Machine Wokes, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    11/12/2000
  - Item 4: Moderie Mfg, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    6/21/1971
  - Item 5: More Shores School District, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    10/31/1969
  - Item 6: Moncanto Research, 1957; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    4/7/1957
  - Item 7: Morton Salt, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    4/7/1959
  - Item 8: Morton Salt, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    11/14/1962
  - Item 9: Morton Salt, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    6/28/1982
  - Item 10: Motor Castings Company, 1956; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    4/11/1956
  - Item 11: Motor Wheel Corporation, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    5/17/1969
  - Item 12: Motor Wheel Corporation, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Motor Wheel Corporation, 1950; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    11/15/1950
  - Item 14: Moynahan Bridget Company, 1956; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    4/18/1956
  - Item 15: Moynahan Bridget Company, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    5/24/1961
  - Item 16: Moynahan Bridget Company, 1965; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    11/22/1965
  - Item 17: Muller Grocieries Baking, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    3/13/1963
  - Item 18: City of Muskegon, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    8/14/2002
  - Item 19: Muskegon Piston Reng Company, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    12/31/1962
  - Item 20: Muskegon Piston Reng Company, 1962; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 5)
    12/1/1962
- Nabisco through National Steel, 1953-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Nabisco Brands vs. American Federation of Grain Millers - Arbitration Award, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 6)
    4/7/1993
  - Item 2: Foster-Forbes Glass Company, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 6)
    2/28/1999
  - Item 3: National R.R. Passenger Corporation - Arbitral, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 6)
    5/31/1998
  - Item 4: Granite Petry Steel Company, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 6)
    11/21/1977
  - Item 5: National Steel Corporation, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 6)
    12/4/1991
- Ned's Auto Supply through Northwest Airlines, 1961-2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Neds Auto Supply Company, Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: New England Telephone & Telegraph Company, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 7)
    1/1/1978
  - Item 3: New Haven Foundry, Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: North Oakland Medical Denter, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 7)
    3/14/2000
- Northwest Steel and Wire through NWS Michigan, 1981-2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: North Western Steel v. Wire Company, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 8)
    7/28/1981
  - Item 2: NWS Michigan, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 8)
    8/18/2001
- Oakland Press through Owens-Illinois, 1961-2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Oakland Press, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    9/16/1974
  - Item 2: Oakland Sand Gravel, 1994; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    6/23/1994
  - Item 3: Oakland Union - School of Business, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    1/8/2002
  - Item 4: City of Oak Park Police, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    12/2/1998
  - Item 5: Occidental Chemichal Corporation, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    6/10/1993
  - Item 6: Oglebay Norton, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    9/14/1968
  - Item 7: Oheleth Taconite, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    6/30/1971
  - Item 8: Oheleth Taconite, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    2/26/1988
  - Item 9: Ohio Corrugating Company, 1980; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    12/30/1980
  - Item 10: Ohio Edision Company, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    2/24/1968
  - Item 11: Ohio Edision Company, 1968; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    6/22/1968
  - Item 12: Ohio Edision Company, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    1/16/1970
  - Item 13: Ohio Lime Company, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    5/10/1961
  - Item 14: Orange County Board of Commerce, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    3/18/1999
  - Item 15: Schol Board of Orange County, Florida, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    5/16/1999
  - Item 16: Evinrude Motors, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 17: Owens - Illinois Glass Company, 1961; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: Owens - Illinois, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 2, Folder 9)
    4/21/1975